unrwa.org 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy | UNRWA

The United Nations Relief and Works Agency is firmly committed to your privacy on the internet. The following describes our policy concerning the gathering and sharing of information through this website. In brief, our policy is as follows:

  * We monitor general trends in the use of our website but do not track individual visitors.
  * We do not collect information concerning individual visitors unless that information is voluntarily disclosed, for example by signing up for our email newsletter.
  * We do not sell or rent information voluntarily disclosed to us, nor do we share it with any third parties except for completing a donation transaction that you initiate.
  * Individuals who sign up for emails will only be contacted by UNRWA for purposes related to the Agency’s work.
  * At any time, visitors who have signed up for a specific service can have their names removed from the relevant mailing list.

#### Normal website usage

In general, you can browse the UNRWA website without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. The only information we collect from a normal website visit is your IP (Internet Protocol) address, domain name, browser type, operating system, and information such as the website that referred you to us, the files you downloaded, the pages you visit, and the dates/times of those visits.

This information is collected on an aggregate basis only. For example, UNRWA tracks which pages are most popular among visitors as a whole, but we do not track information on which pages an individual visitor might look at during a visit to our site. We do not collect any other information - such as the name, mailing address, email address, or phone number of the visitor - without the visitor's knowledge and permission.

All information that we collect is used for internal review only and not shared with third parties. We use this information to analyse trends and measure site activity to improve the usefulness of the site to our visitors.

#### **Collection of personally identifiable information**

If you sign up for a newsletter, donate online, request information, provide feedback, or apply for a job, you will be asked to provide personal information such as your name, postal address and email address. This information is collected only with your knowledge and permission, and is kept in various UNRWA databases. If you donate online, you will be asked to provide your credit card details.

Personally identifiable information that you provide in this way will not be given to any third parties except for the use of completing a donation transaction that you initiate.

UNRWA takes great care to keep the details you provide for credit card payments confidential. We use RBS WorldPay, which ensures an optimum level of security. To prevent fraud, your data is encrypted and then transmitted automatically and directly to the credit card issuer, who processes the payment.

#### **More answers to questions about donations**

 What if I do not want to provide personal information?

Providing personal information on the UNRWA website is optional. If you choose not to provide personal information, you can still browse and use the UNRWA site, but you will not be able to carry out certain actions such as donating online, registering for a newsletter, or applying for a job.

#### Opting out

People who provide an email address and/or donate via the website may receive UNRWA’s electronic newsletter. Each edition includes an option to remove your address from the mailing list and you may also opt out by contacting us with the subject line 'opt out’.

#### Disclaimer

This site contains hypertext links to other sites. The UNRWA assumes no responsibility for those sites including the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

While UNRWA makes every effort to ensure that any material available to be downloaded from UNRWA’s website is free of any software virus, it cannot guarantee that the material is free from any or all software viruses. UNRWA is not responsible for any loss or damage howsoever caused by the software and related codes, including viruses and worms.

##### Contact

For questions or queries regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at [hq-pio@unrwa.org](mailto:hq-pio@unrwa.org).
